## Anudeep G.I

Address: S/O S.Gopala

Bovikana P.O Muliyar

Kasargod

E-mail: anu1488@gmail.com

Mobile: +91 9995875262/+91 8921720345

## **Professional summary**

Web Developer specializing in both front end development and back end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web Application. Well-versed in PHP,javascript and Codeigniter(MVC), jquery, bootstrap,mysql, Strong background Building Web application from scratch.

#### **Education Qualification:**

- Bachelor of Computer Application (Mangalore University) [2007-2010]
- Android Application Development
- Diploma in Animation & VFX(Mangalore University)

## **Work History**

# Senior Software Developer in Diya System. 2016 - Currently Working

#### ipage.com

- Psd to html converting
- Sass
- Javascript/jquery
- Perl(mason framework)

#### bluehost.com

- Psd to html converting
- Javascript/jquery
- Sass
- Perl(mason framework)

#### hostgator.com

- Psd to html converting
- Javascript/jquery
- Sass
- Perl(mason framework)

#### netfirms.com

- Psd to html converting
- Javascript/jquery
- Sass
- Perl(mason framework)

#### hostgator.com

- Psd to html converting
- jquery

- Sass

#### **EEP 3.0**

- Reactis

## Junior Software Developer in BillMail ID Pvt. Ltd.

2011- Past [1-8-2011 to 30-1-2013]

## Software Engineer Codecraft Technology

Past [1-8-2011 to 30-1-2013]

#### Codecraft.co.in

- Worked on re-designing of codecraft home page

#### Maville

- Admin panel and web service
- Boostrap 3
- Codeigniter(MVC ,PHP)
- Jquery,javascript,ajax
- Databse design
- Integrated weather api
- Web Service

#### fanspectrum.com

- Javascript ,jquery- bugfixing
- Php bugfixing
- UI CSS biufixing

#### renault.co.nz

- Converted psd to theme silverstripe -php

#### Birthdaybuddy

- Admin panel
- Push notification
- Web Services

#### **Demo projects for clients**

- Worked in Wordpress for client
- Phonegap

## Software Engineer Gigaquirks (Work From home)

[1-4-2014 to 31-7-2015]

#### select.gigaquirks.com

- Database design
- Codeigniter(php,MVC)
- javscript,jquery,ajax, fullcalendar.js
- Boostrap 3
- CSS
- html

#### Other works

 Worpress- jquery ,javascript and many javascript library dependence on client requirement

- Magento bugfix
- Jquery animation site

**Self- Learning : -** aws, nodejs, expressjs, Mongo DB

#### Skill

#### Server Side Programming

- PHP(Codeigniter)
- Ruby On Rails (Experience level Beginner )

#### Front End Development

- Javascript
- jQuery
- Boostrap
- CSS
- HTML5
- Worked with many JS library Based on requirement

#### <u>Servers</u>

- AWS
- Openshift
- Godaddy

#### <u>CMS</u>

- Wordpress
- SilverStrip

#### **Database**

MySql

#### <u>IDE</u>

- Sublime
- Netbeans

## Other Tool Knowledge

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator , Visual Basics, Android SDK, Dreamviewer, Adobe Flash, 3D MAX, Autodesk MAYA, Adobe After Effect, Sound Forge , Windows XP/Vista/7 , Linux, Ubantu , Mac

## **Strengths**

- Hard Working, fully devoted to work undertaken
- Quest for learning
- Able to work individual as well in a team.

#### **Personal Details**

Name : Anudeep G.I

Father's Name : S.Gopala

Date Of Birth : 14/11/1988

Marital Status : Single

Nationality : Indian

Languages Known: English [R/W/S], Hindi[R/W/S], Kannada[R/W/S], Malayalam[S], Tulu[S]

Address : S/O S.Gopala

Bovikana P.O Muliyar Kasaragod

Phone : 04998-250646 Mobile : 09995875262

e-mail : <u>anu1488@gmail.com</u>

(Anudeep)